LUCY NYANDOYA WERE

Mobile: +254710526569

Email: nyandoyawere@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/lucywere

SUMMARY

I am a highly personable team player and great at handling various tasks, including office management, scheduling, and documentation. I am proficient in Google Workspace and ERP systems, with strong skills in data management, report preparation, and communication.

I also have experience in procurement, inventory management, and coordination with various stakeholders to ensure the timely delivery of products and services. Recognized for a commitment to maintaining high service standards, excellent problem-solving abilities, and a proactive approach to supporting team objectives.

I am recognised for my commitment to maintaining high service standards, excellent problem-solving abilities, and a proactive approach to supporting team objectives.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- 1. Improved supplier turnaround time from 4 to 2 weeks, enhancing proper resource and financial planning.
- 2. Led a team of six staff members in the supply department that successfully transitioned goods in six warehouses internationally.
- 3. Effectively implemented the use of Microsoft Excel to develop inventory tracking spreadsheets to minimize inventory loss and help in forecasting.
- 4. Successfully processed and managed over 4, 000 records per month, ensuring accuracy and timeliness.

SKILLS

Information Management, Interpersonal Skills, Effective Communication, Excellent administrative abilities, Organizing and prioritizing work, Adaptability and flexibility, Problem-Solving Skills, Data Integrity, Supplier Relationship Management, Warehouse Management, ERP systems proficiency, Supplier Negotiations, Attention to detail, Teamwork and collaboration, Demand Forecasting, Stress Management.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan 2024 To Date: Executive Virtual Assistant-Remote, Freelance

- Calendar Management: Effectively scheduled more than 12 meetings and appointments per month, improving time management by 25%.
- Coordination of Communications: Managed all incoming correspondence, including phone calls and emails, and guaranteed a 95% satisfaction rating from internal stakeholders.
- Travel Arrangements: Through clever vendor negotiations, I was able to save 15% on airfare and accommodation for over 2 business visits per month.
- Preparing and editing important documents and presentations for executive meetings improved the quality of deliverables and reduced preparation time by 30%.
- Project Support: Research and data collection for strategic initiatives helped with project management, resulting in successful project planning for my client.

April 2023 To Oct 2023: Supply Chain Supervisor

Medecins Sans Frontieres (MSF), Holland

- Enhanced Supplier Management: kept an updated list of 40+ suppliers and conducted yearly evaluations and weekly follow-ups on purchase orders, claims, and complaints.
- Executed procurement: managed 20 internal purchase orders and 10 external orders biweekly.
- Supervised a team of 6 storekeepers handling 3 medical, 2 logistical, and 1 cold chain warehouse.
- Coordinated the transport and customs clearance of 4 shipments weekly.

April 2022 To March 2023: Order Processing Officer

Medecins Sans Frontieres (MSF), Holland

- Focal person for all orders and supplies.
- Creating authorized documents for ordering and receptions weekly.
- Identifying stock items at risk of rupturing bimonthly.
- Daily updating of the supply database, Unifield, with all supply documentation and processes.
- Daily filing and quarterly archiving of supply documents.

Sep. 2020 To March 2022: Medical Data Processing Officer

Medecins Sans Frontieres (MSF), France

- Handled 550 records for research participants using Redcap.
- Effectively maintained research supply inventory for 550 participants and 10 staff members. Set up quality assurance and control on the 550 records according to the standards of good clinical practice (GCP).
- Achieved high levels of data safety through the use of antivirus and password-protected computers.

Feb. 2020-Aug. 2020: Health Management Information Systems Assistant

Impact Research and Development Organization (IRDO)

- I reviewed, analyzed, and validated data for 5 sub-counties in the region.
- I generated monthly reports by the 1st of every month and then conducted monthly data review meetings.
- Data Management: Maintained proper documentation of 450 patients to assist in standardizing data management procedures.

October 2015-Sept 2019: Data Management Clerk/Receptionist

International Centre for AIDS Programme (ICAP)/MOH

- Facilitated daily client scheduling and management of 250 clients.
- Data entry of 250 patient records into the IQ Care system and 2800 patients into OpenMRS. Ensured daily documentation of ART, HEI tracking log, viral load, and MCH registers with between 20 and 50 records.
- Reporting: Generated monthly 731 and DHIS2 reports.
- Quality Assurance: Performed Data Quality Audits (DQA) on more than 3,000 patient files and records.

Apr 2010-August 2015: Data Clerk

Kenya Medical Research Institute (KEMRI/CDC)

- Enhanced direct data Entry of 250 records daily by scanning using Teleforms.
- Championed weekly data cleaning to prevent critical errors.
- Implemented the daily production of 3–10 patient clinical alerts.

EDUCATION

Diploma in Business Management; The Kenya Institute of Management

REFEREES Available Upon Request.